<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Firebase-Clemenisle-EV</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="FirebaseURL">
        https://fir-clemenisle-ev-default-rtdb.asia-southeast1.firebasedatabase.app/
    </string>
    <string name="originLocationMarkTitle">
        Your Location
    </string>
    <string name="helpEntryNote">
        The answers/solutions to your questions/problems will be posted in FAQ section.
        So make sure you will always check the updates here.
        \nThe more entries that are similar to your entry, the faster the admins will answer your questions.
        It is just a matter of urgency.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess1">
        When the schedule of your Booking comes,
        please do the following:
        \n● Prepare your payment.
        \n● Go to your designated Starting Station.
        \n● Always check on the chat between you and the driver regarding on possible concerns.
        \n● Find the plate number of your assigned driver\'s E-Vehicle.
        \n● Show and let your assigned driver scan the QR Code of your booking record.
        \n● Please check carefully the status of your booking record. It should become \"Completed\".
        \n● Settle the payment.
        \n● Ride into the E-Vehicle with your assigned driver.
        \n● Have fun.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess2">
        You can only cancel your booking while it is \"Processing\".
        Once the status becomes \"Booked\", you cannot cancel it anymore.
        Please be sure of your decision and please be polite as always.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess3">
        Things to do while waiting for your assigned driver:
        \n● Prepare your payment.
        \n● Do not leave your current position.
        \n● Always check on the chat between you and the driver regarding on possible concerns.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess4">
        Things to do when your assigned driver arrived:
        \n● Validate the plate number of your assigned driver\'s E-Vehicle.
        \n● Show and let your assigned driver scan the QR Code of your booking record.
        \n● Please check carefully the status of your booking record. It should become \"Completed\".
        \n● Settle the payment.
        \n● Ride into the E-Vehicle with your assigned driver.
        \n● Have fun.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess5">
        If your booking record is still \"Processing\" for 10 minutes,
        it will be mark automatically as \"Failed\",
        but you are freely to cancel your booking before then.
        Once the status becomes \"Booked\", you are only able to cancel it
        if the driver is not yet arrived by 10 minutes since the time of the schedule of your booking.
        Until then, please consider waiting for your driver and send kind regards before cancelling.
        Please be polite as always.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment1">
        Online Payment must be settled until 24 HOURS BEFORE THE BOOKING SCHEDULE,
        to give the admins a suitable amount of time to confirm the payment details.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment2">
        The online payment is through G-Cash Application.
        \nHere are the steps to process your online payment.
        \n● Go to the booking record of your desire with a status of \"Processing\" or \"Booked\" in order to access the online payment.
        \n● Tap on the online payment button to go to the online payment screen.
        \n● Send your payment based on the amount cost of your booked tour to the numbers showed on the online payment screen.
        \n● Retrieve the transaction\'s reference number and add it in the reference number list.
        \n● Tap on the confirm button and wait for the admin to process your online payment.
        \n● The refund will automatically sent if you cancelled your booking or failed to go to the tour.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment3">
        Avoid paying online if you are being indecisive about
        going to your booked tour to prevent any inconvenience.
    </string>
</resources>