<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Firebase-Clemenisle-EV</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="FirebaseURL">
        https://fir-clemenisle-ev-default-rtdb.asia-southeast1.firebasedatabase.app/
    </string>
    <string name="originLocationMarkTitle">
        Your Location
    </string>
    <string name="helpEntryNote">
        The answers/solutions to your questions/problems will be posted in FAQ section.
        So make sure you will always check the updates here.
        \nThe more entries that are similar to your entry, the faster the admins will answer your questions.
        It is just a matter of urgency.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess1">
        When the schedule of your Booking comes,
        please do the following:
        \n• Prepare your payment.
        \n• Go to your designated Starting Station.
        \n• Find the plate number of your assigned driver\'s E-Vehicle.
        \n• Validate your Booking ID and then status should become \"Completed\".
        \n• Ride into the E-Vehicle with your assigned driver.
    </string>
    <string name="bookingProcess2">
        You can only cancel your booking while it is \"Processing\".
        Once the status becomes \"Booked\", you cannot cancel it anymore.
        Please be sure of your decision.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment1">
        Online Payment must be settled until 24 HOURS BEFORE THE BOOKING SCHEDULE,
        to give the admins a suitable amount of time to confirm the payment details.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment2">
        The online payment is through G-Cash Application.
        \nHere are the steps to process your online payment.
        \n• Go to the booking record of your desire with a status of \"Processing\" or \"Booked\" in order to access the online payment.
        \n• Tap on the online payment button to go to the online payment screen.
        \n• Send your payment depending on the amount cost of your booked tour to the numbers showed on the online payment screen.
        \n• Retrieve the transaction\'s reference number and put it in the input box.
        \n• Tap on the confirm button and wait for the admin to process your online payment.
        \n• You can request for a refund if you cancelled your booking or failed to go to the tour.
    </string>
    <string name="onlinePayment3">
        Avoid paying online if you are being indecisive about
        going to your booked tour to prevent any inconvenience.
    </string>
</resources>